{"data":[{"question":"________ of Shakespeare's plays are about history.","a":"A few of","b":"Many","c":"Much","d":"A little","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0\n- \"A few\" not \"a few of\".\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"They spent ________ time studying Victorian literature.","a":"few","b":"many","c":"a large number of","d":"much","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many\/a large number of: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"________ popular expressions in our language have interesting background.","a":"Little","b":"Many","c":"A large number","d":"Much","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many\/a large number of: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"At the beginning everybody spoke English very quickly and I couldn't understand ________. But after ________ days, it is easier and ________ things I had learnt came back to me.","a":"much \/ a few \/ many","b":"a lot \/ little \/ a lot","c":"much \/ much \/ a great number","d":"many \/ a few \/ many","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Much\/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many\/a large number of: countable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"They ________ in New York next week.","a":"arrive","b":"will arrive","c":"has arrived","d":"have arrived","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple Future tense (next week).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"This is the best performance of Hamlet that I ________ in years.","a":"had seen","b":"saw","c":"have seen","d":"see","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense (the first\/the most...that...).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"They ________ that you are going to be late.","a":"will know","b":"know","c":"knew","d":"have known","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: expresses general fact.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The people that I ________ here have been very friendly.","a":"to meet","b":"meet","c":"have met","d":"had met","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple Past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past. Sometimes, the speaker may not actually mention the specific time, but they do have one specific time in mind.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The plug has come out of the ________.","a":"sock","b":"socket","c":"socking","d":"soccer","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Socket: the place on a piece of electrical equipment that you put a plug or a light bulb into.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"She says that she ________ the bill next week.","a":"pays","b":"will pay","c":"has paid","d":"is paying","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple future tense.\u00a0\n\"Will\" is usually used in promises.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}